### **Buhle Lusizi**

# **RESUME**



No.2 Parkhof Grant Street Kenilworth 7708

0670749343 buhleomuhlelusizi@gmail.com

### **PROFILE**

I am a Web development candidate supervisor at Younglings Africa.

I have the following experience:

R - 2 months

JavaScript - 6 months

Python(machine learning) - 5 months

HTML - 1 year CSS - 1 year

Pastel Accounting - 1 year Microsoft Excel - 1 year

My goal is to be the best in Web development while learning Data Science.

JOB APPLIED FOR

Web developer

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020 - 2021 Younglings Africa(Yes4Youth)/ Web development Supervisor/ I

manage discord candidate meetings and I make sure that they

submit their weekly and monthly activities.

2019 - 2019 Crystal concepts/ Assistant administrator/ I handled their social

media pages and i managed to increase their social media

followers from 20% to 98%.

### **EDUCATION**

2021 - 2021 Nobel Explorers Leadership Training

2020 - 2021 Codetelligent

2017 - 2019 Northlink College

2014 - 2016 Mandela School of Science and Technology

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Isixhosa Zulu Sotho Tswana

# **HOBBIES**

Coding Reading Writing Singing

## **SKILLS**

HTML CSS JavaScript

Python(machine learning)

**Pastel Accounting** 

R

Microsoft Excel

### **REFERENCES**

Zizipho Sontshete

Supervisor

e-mail: zizipho.sontshete@younglings.africa

Keoikantse Botlholo Codetelligent C.E.O

e-mail: keoikantsebotlholo@codetelligent.org

### **OTHER**

Achievements

Codetelligent: HTML/ CSS Fundamentals Freecode camp: Responsive Web certificate Freecode camp: Machine learning Python

Solo learn: HTML and CSS